

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

### **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and dung no? Chung ta van biết rằng, làm việc với một đoạn văn bản dễ đọc và rõ nghĩa dễ of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

### **EDUCATION**



#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. crambled, nonsensical Latin derived from Cicero's 1st-century BC text De Finibus Bonorum et Malo administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

#### **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

# **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

# Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult m hon s and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

# Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and
- Assist to , that they cannot foresee the pain and trouble that are bound to ensue; and equal blame belo goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

# **ACTIVITIES**



Sep 2003 - 2007

#### **CVPRO JSC**

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer ng' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

# **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

# HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO

2013 - 2014

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US , "Um, not so fast." The placeholder text, beginning wit

# **REFERENCES**



### **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

# **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop

Excel English

Power Point Japanese

# **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt m. Cicero's De finibus bonorum et malorum CICERO'S
   DE FINIBUS OPENING PAGE SECTION 1.10.32 OF CICE and US student's life
   experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities